Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical files
  - 1978
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 66)
    - Naval Officer Education Program (Box 66)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 66)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 66)
    - News Service (Box 66)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 66)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 66)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 66)
    - Orientation, Office of Personnel (Box 66)
    - Pharmacy, College of Philosophy (Box 66)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 66)
    - Physical Education (Box 66)
    - Physical Properties, Department of (Box 66)
    - Physics (Box 66)
    - Political Science (Box 66)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Box 66)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 66)
    - President, Office of (Box 66)
    - President, National Association (Box 66)
    - Psychiatry (Box 66)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 66)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 66)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 66)
    - Publications Office (Box 66)
    - Radiology (Box 66)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 66)
    - Regents (Box 66)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 66)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 66)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President (Box 66)
    - Research Seminar In Quantitative Economics (Box 67)
    - Residential College (Box 67)
    - Rose Bowl (Box 67)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 67)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 67)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 67)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 67)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 67)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 67)
    - Security Offices (Box 67)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 67)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 67)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 67)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 67)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 67)
    - Speech, Communication and Theater (Box 67)
    - Speech Clinic (Box 67)
    - State Relations and Planning (Box 67)
    - Student Activities (Box 67)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 67)
    - Student Publications (Box 67)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 67)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 67)
    - Unions (Box 67)
    - University Activities Center (Box 67)
    - University Housing (Box 67)
    - University Musical Society (Box 67)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 67)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 67)
    - University Relations (Box 67)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 67)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 67)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 67)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 67)
    - WUOM Radio Station (Box 67)
  - 1979
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 68)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 68)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 68)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 68)
    - Alumni Association (Box 68)
    - Anthropology (Box 68)
    - Applied Mechanics and Engineering Science (Box 68)
    - Appropriations (Box 68)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 68)
    - Art, School of (Box 68)
    - Asian Studies (Box 68)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 68)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 68)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 68)
    - Bands (Box 68)
    - Biological Sciences (Box 68)
    - Biological Station (Box 68)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 68)
    - Budget (Box 68)
    - Buildings (Box 68)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 68)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 68)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 68)
    - Chemistry (Box 68)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 68)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 68)
    - Classical Studies (Box 68)
    - Commencement (Box 68)
    - Commission for Women (Box 68)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 68)
    - Committees (Box 68)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 68)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 68)
    - Continuing Engineering Education (Box 68)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 68)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 68)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 68)
    - Development Office (Box 68)
    - Economic Outlook Conference (Box 68)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 68)
    - Education, School of (Box 68)
    - Electrical and Computer Science (Box 68)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 68)
    - English (LSA) (Box 69)
    - English Language Institute (Box 69)
    - Enrollment (Box 69)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 69)
    - Extension Service (Box 69)
    - Faculty (Box 69)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 69)
    - Fees (Box 69)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 69)
    - Fishery, Forestry and Wildlife Program (Box 69)
    - Flint College (Box 69)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 69)
    - Geography (Box 69)
    - Geological Science (Box 69)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 69)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 69)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 69)
    - Grants and Contracts (Box 69)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (Box 69)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 69)
    - Group Dynamics, Center for Research (Box 69)
    - Health Service (Box 69)
    - Higher Education, Center for Study of (Box 69)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 69)
    - History (LSA) (Box 69)
    - History of Art (Box 69)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 69)
    - Honors (Box 69)
    - Faculty (Box 69)
    - Student (Box 69)
    - Honors Council (Box 69)
    - Topical files (cont.), 1979 (Box 69)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 69)
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of and Program in (Box 69)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute of (Box 69)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 69)
    - Humanities (Engineering College) (Box 69)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 69)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 69)
    - Interlochen (Box 69)
    - International Center (Box 69)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 69)
    - Journalism (LSA) (Box 69)
    - Judiciary (Box 69)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 69)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 69)
    - Landscape Architecture (Box 69)
    - Law School (Box 69)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 69)
    - Legislative Research Center (Box 69)
    - Legislature (Michigan) (Box 69)
    - Libraries (Box 69)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 69)
    - Linguistics (Box 69)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 70)
    - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering (Box 70)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 70)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 70)
    - Media Resources Center (Box 70)
    - Medical School (Box 70)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 70)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of (Box 70)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 70)
    - Michigan League (Box 70)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 70)
    - Michigan Union (Box 70)
    - Microbiology (Box 70)
    - Minority Groups (Box 70)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 70)
    - Museum of Art (Box 70)
    - Museum of Paleontology (Box 70)
    - Museum of Zoology (Box 70)
    - Music, School of (also 1978) (Box 70)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 70)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 70)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 70)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 70)
    - News Service (News and Information Services) (Box 70)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 70)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 70)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 70)
    - Ophthalmology (Box 70)
    - Otorhinolaryngology (Box 70)
    - Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases (Box 70)
    - Personnel (Box 70)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 70)
    - Philosophy (Box 70)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 70)
    - Physical Education (Box 70)
    - Physical Properties, Department of (Box 70)
    - Physics (Box 71)
    - Political Science (Box 71)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 71)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Box 71)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 71)
    - President, Office of (Box 71)
    - President, National Association (Box 71)
    - Presidential Search (Box 71)
    - Psychiatry (Box 71)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 71)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 71)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 71)
    - Publications Office (Box 71)
    - Radiology (Box 71)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 71)
    - Regents (Box 71)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 71)
    - Republican National Convention, 1980 (Box 71)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 71)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President (also 1980) (Box 71)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 71)
    - Residential College (Box 71)
    - Rose Bowl (Box 71)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 71)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 71)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 71)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 71)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 71)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 71)
    - Security Offices (Box 71)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 71)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 71)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 71)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 72)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 72)
    - Sociology (Box 72)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 72)
    - Speech, Communication and Theater (Box 72)
    - Staff Records Office (Box 72)
    - State Relations and Planning (Box 72)
    - Student Activities (Box 72)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 72)
    - Student Publications (Box 72)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 72)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 72)
    - Unions (Box 72)
    - University Activities Center (Box 72)
    - University Housing (Box 72)
    - University Musical Society (Box 72)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 72)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 72)
    - University Relations (Box 72)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 72)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 72)
    - William L. Clements Library (Box 72)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 72)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 72)
    - WUOM (Box 72)
  - 1980
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 73)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 73)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 73)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 73)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 73)
    - Alumni Association (Box 73)
    - Anthropology (Box 73)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 73)
    - Art, School of (Box 73)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 73)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 73)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 73)
    - Bands (Box 73)
    - Biological Sciences (Box 73)
    - Biological Station (Box 73)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 73)
    - Budget (Box 73)
    - Buildings (Box 73)
    - Bush Program in Child Development (Box 73)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 73)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 73)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 73)
    - Chemistry (Box 73)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 73)
    - Classical Studies (Box 73)
    - Commencement, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Commission for Women (Box 73)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 73)
    - Topical files (cont.), 1980 (Box 73)
    - Committees (Box 73)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 73)
    - Computing Center (Box 73)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 73)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 73)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 73)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 73)
    - Development Office (Box 73)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 73)
    - Education, School of (Box 73)
    - Electrical and Computer Science (Box 74)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 74)
    - English (LSA) (Box 74)
    - English Composition Board (Box 74)
    - English Language Institute (Box 74)
    - Enrollment (Box 74)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 74)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 74)
    - Extension Service (Box 74)
    - Faculty (Box 74)
    - Fees (Box 74)
    - Financial (Box 74)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 74)
    - Flint College, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 74)
    - Geography (Box 74)
    - Geological Science (Box 74)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 74)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 74)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 74)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (Box 74)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 74)
    - Health Service (Box 74)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 74)
    - History of Art (Box 74)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 74)
    - Honors (Box 74)
    - Faculty (Box 74)
    - Student (Box 74)
    - Honors Council (Box 74)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 74)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute of (Box 74)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 74)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 74)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 74)
    - International Center (Box 74)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 74)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 74)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 74)
    - Law School (Box 74)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 75)
    - Legislature (Michigan) (Box 75)
    - Libraries (Box 75)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 75)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 75)
    - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering (Box 75)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 75)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 75)
    - Media Resources Center (Box 75)
    - Medical Care Organization (Box 75)
    - Medical School, 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 75)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of (Box 75)
    - Michigan Educational Research Information Triad (Box 75)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 75)
    - Michigan League (Box 75)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 75)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 75)
    - Michigan Union (Box 75)
    - Microbiology (Box 75)
    - Minority Groups (Box 75)
    - Museum of Art (Box 75)
    - Museum of Paleontology (Box 75)
    - Museum of Zoology (Box 75)
    - Music, School of (Box 75)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 75)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 75)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 75)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 75)
    - Neurology (Box 75)
    - News Service (News and Information Services) (Box 75)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 75)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 75)
    - Personnel (Box 75)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 75)
    - Philosophy (Box 75)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 75)
    - Physical Education (Box 75)
    - Physical Properties, Department of (Box 75)
    - Physics (Box 75)
    - Political Science (Box 75)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 75)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 75)
    - President, Office of (Box 75)
    - President, National Association (Box 75)
    - Psychiatry (Box 75)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 75)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 75)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 75)
    - Publications Office (Box 75)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 75)
    - Regents (Box 75)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 75)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 76)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 76)
    - Residential College (Box 76)
    - Romance Languages and Literature (Box 76)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 76)
    - Russel (Henry) Lectureship and awards (Box 76)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 76)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 76)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 76)
    - Security Offices (Box 76)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 76)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 76)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 76)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 76)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 76)
    - Sociology (Box 76)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 76)
    - Staff Relations and Planning (Box 76)
    - State Relations and Planning (Box 76)
    - Student Activities (Box 76)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 76)
    - Student Publications (Box 76)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 76)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 76)
    - Unions (Box 76)
    - University Activities Center (Box 76)
    - University Housing (Box 76)
    - University Musical Society (Box 76)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 76)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 76)
    - University Relations (Box 76)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 76)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 76)
    - William L. Clements Library (Box 76)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 76)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 76)
    - WUOM (Box 76)
  - 1981
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 80)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 80)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 80)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 80)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 80)
    - Alumni Association (Box 80)
    - Anthropology (Box 80)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 80)
    - Art, School of (Box 80)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, Department of (Box 80)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 80)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 80)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 80)
    - Biological Sciences (Box 80)
    - Biological Station (Box 80)
    - Biophysics Research Division (Box 80)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 80)
    - Budget (Box 80)
    - Buildings (Box 80)
    - Bush Program in Child Development (Box 80)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 80)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 80)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 80)
    - Chemistry (Box 80)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 80)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 80)
    - Classical Studies (Box 80)
    - Clements, William L. Library (Box 80)
    - Commencement (Box 80)
    - Commission for Women (Box 80)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 80)
    - Committees (Box 80)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 80)
    - Communications, Office of (Box 80)
    - Computing Center (Box 80)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 80)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 80)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 80)
    - Dental Research Institute (Box 80)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 80)
    - Development Office (Box 80)
    - Economic Outlook Conference (Box 80)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 81)
    - Education, School of (Box 81)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 81)
    - English (LSA) (Box 81)
    - English Composition Board (Box 81)
    - English Language Institute (Box 81)
    - Enrollment (Box 81)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 81)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 81)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 81)
    - Extension Service (Box 81)
    - Faculty (Box 81)
    - Fees (Box 81)
    - Financial (Box 81)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 81)
    - Flint College (Box 81)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 81)
    - General Counsel (Box 81)
    - Geography (Box 81)
    - Geological Science (Box 81)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 81)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 81)
    - Government Relations (Box 81)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 81)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 81)
    - Group Dynamics, Center for Research (Box 81)
    - Health Service (Box 81)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of (Box 81)
    - History (Box 81)
    - History of Art (Box 81)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 82)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 82)
    - Honors
      - Faculty (Box 82)
      - Student (Box 82)
    - Honors Council (Box 82)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 82)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute of (Box 82)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 82)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 82)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 82)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political Research (Box 82)
    - International Center (Box 82)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 82)
    - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation Institute (Box 82)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 82)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 82)
    - Law School (Box 82)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 82)
    - Libraries (Box 82)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 82)
    - Linguistics (Box 82)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 82)
    - Medical School (Box 82)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 82)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of (Box 82)
    - Michigan Business Review (Box 82)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 82)
    - Michigan Law Review (Box 82)
    - Michigan League (Box 82)
    - Michigan Media Resource Center (Box 82)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 82)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 82)
    - Michigan Union (Box 82)
    - Minority Groups (Box 82)
    - Museum of Art (Box 82)
    - Music, School of (Box 82)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 82)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 82)
    - News Service (News and Information Services) (Box 83)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 83)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 83)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 83)
    - Personnel (Box 83)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 83)
    - Philosophy (Box 83)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 83)
    - Physical Education (Box 83)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 83)
    - Physics (Box 83)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 83)
    - Political Science (Box 83)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 83)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 83)
    - President, Office of (Box 83)
    - President, National Association (Box 83)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 83)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 83)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 83)
    - Regents (Box 83)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 83)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President for (Box 83)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 83)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 83)
    - Residential College (Box 83)
    - Romance Languages and Literature (Box 83)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 83)
    - Russel, Henry, Lectures Awards (Box 83)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 83)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 83)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 83)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 83)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 83)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 83)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 83)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 83)
    - Sociology (Box 83)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 83)
    - Statistics (Box 83)
    - Student Activities (Box 83)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 84)
    - Student Publications (Box 84)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 84)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 84)
    - Theater and Drama, Department of (Box 84)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 84)
    - University Musical Society (Box 84)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 84)
    - Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for Research on (Box 84)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 84)
    - William L. Clements Library (Box 84)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 84)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 84)
    - WUOM (Box 84)
  - 1982
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 84)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 84)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 84)